hello everyone and welcome to the dr
phil show
i am your host Doctor phil
today we're here with a special guest
her name is hannah
she is having family troubles and she
has come here to share it with all of us
now hannah what is it that's bothering
you I see you have a black eye did your
mommy or daddy
punch you in the face no it wasn't them
it was my brother Jimmy he did it
it's always him I see would you explain
to us a little about this Jimmy before
we proceed
he's always pissed he's always just not
happy
he's always irritated with something
you know and just straight up not having
it it's too much for our parents to
handle
last week we went to Sunday church and
he climbed up on the altar
he then shouted that he is the
embodiment of the devil and he pulled
down his pants
and started to spray his disgusting [ __ ]
all over the place
all I want is to have my kind brother
back the one who would laugh
and play with me
you have nothing to worry about now
hannah that is why we are here
now let's bring out Jimmy so the two of
you could have a nice sock
oh no Jimmy you mean he's here please
don't bring him out he'll hit me again
hannah you will never settle your
differences if you keep running away
I'm sure your brother wants to make
amends just as much as you do
won't you give them a chance you might
be right okay i'll try my best
Doctor phil
now everyone please welcome in hannah's
brother Jimmy
[Music]
[ __ ] all of you you don't know me none
of you know me
the devil has entered my body and
through me I have the power over you all
so you need to stop Jimmy
can you please just sit down no [ __ ] off
don't make me rape you i'll do it i'll
[ __ ] do it right here in front of
everyone
Chinese
now that things have settled down Jimmy
do you know why you're here
because my sister is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
look what he's wearing doctor it's the
middle of [ __ ] July
this [ __ ] acting like halloween is the
day after tomorrow
Jimmy why are you wearing that exactly
can't you see you might scare or
possibly offend someone
i wear it because I'm a [ __ ] hardcore
son of a [ __ ]
the devil came to me in my Sleet he
looked me in the eye and said
Jimmy you're one sexy piece of ass I was
all like
i know [ __ ] now get out of my house i
need to go trick or treating
you see what I'm dealing with he's like
this the whole time we're at home
he acts like every day is halloween and
he uses it to scare me
and and beat me up
oh please [ __ ] she's lying i'll tell
you what really happens at home
yesterday I was going to go poop so i
was unplugging the living room tv
so I could take it with me into the
bathroom while I take a huge ass [ __ ]
dump and [ __ ]
i like to watch the halloweentown movies
while I take a [ __ ]
when I opened the door I saw hannah
right there getting [ __ ] in the ass by
the scary Godmother
hannah is this true
this isn't about me doctor this is about
my brother getting the help he needs
see what she does she always pushes the
blame on others
she never takes responsibility get off
the stage
[Music]
you're retired can't you see I'm hauling
us
get out of my way
hey now that's no way to talk to our
master
i think someone owes an apology
master what are you some kind of a group
well I'm not scared
patience boy we have not come to fight
we come for a very special offering
one that if you choose to accept we will
grant you mercy
oh yeah what is this offer for that
question
you must ask one of my [ __ ]
okay fine i'll play your little game
play you what's this all about
we are a group of individuals who share
a common goal
long ago the timeline itself was altered
and we have come to alter it again
or rather to fix it
timeline that sounds like a load of
garbage to me why are you even here
that's simple Jimmy
it's because you two have been hurt hurt
by them
the Sonic Underground
you can exact your revenge and all you
need to do is join us
hey I like what you're selling all right
I'm in
then neil kneel before your new kings
let it be known that from here on out
that you Jimmy are a member of
of the new boys
i see it is just as I suspected this
battle is far from over
and a storm is coming it was a good
thing I put a trekking beacon in that
tomato
it will prove useful in the times ahead
be sure to like and subscribe and don't
forget to comment on who you think these
mysterious toys are
also remember to join Tamers1234512345's
patreon as it helps him deliver great
content